

SOFT SKILLS

- Attention to detail
- Problem-solving
- Collaboration
- Creativity
- Time management
- Adaptability and flexibility
- Receptive to feedback

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Game Development: Unity, C#
- 3D & Art: Blender, Maya, Photoshop, Illustrator, Substance Painter
- Web Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL
- Office Tools: Google Suite, Microsoft Office Suite, Canva
- Additional: Figma, Premiere Pro, Git, Fusion 2

LINKS

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/nateflorendo

Portfolio:

neytism.github.io

Github:

www.github.com/neytism

REFERENCES

Joevi Adrian Oroceo

Senior Game Developer and Part Time Instructor

+63 999 380 5783 adrian.oroceo@ciit.edu.ph

Rodolfo Lopez

Former SMHS Marketing Officer and Artisan Guild Adviser/Trainer

+63 955 045 2278 rblopez04@gmail.com

Nicole Kyle T. De Leon

Game Developer and Multimedia Designer

+63 955 897 2888 nicolekyle.deleon@gmail.com

NATE JUSTINE M. **Florendo**

GAME DEVELOPER AND MULTIMEDIA ARTIST



12 Marigman Road, Antipolo City Brgy. San Roque, Rizal, Philippines



+63 912 437 3613



nateflorendo@gmail.com

PROFILE

Passionate game developer and multimedia artist with 5 years of experience in Unity3D and C# programming, backed by 4+ years of 3D modeling experience. Successfully delivered multiple independent game projects while maintaining academic excellence in Entertainment and Multimedia Computing. Combines technical proficiency with artistic skills to create engaging gaming experiences, with demonstrated ability in both 2D and 3D game development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

April 2021 - March 2022

FREELANCE 3D ARTIST

- Created the storyboards, 3D models, and animations for Singapore International School of Bangkok.
- Created 3D product mockups for Coolab Concept Studio.
- Created 3D models and renderings for **OneZo Tapioca** Antipolo Branch.
- September 2019 November 2020

FREELANCE GRAPHIC ARTIST

• Created menus, promotional materials, and posters for **Kyla and Blanche**.

November 2019 - March 2020

STUDENT INTERN IN QUALITY ASSURANCE DEPARTMENT

 Encoded and organized files, spreadsheets, and reports for Ashford Pharmaceutical Laboratories Inc.

EDUCATION

2021 - Present

CIIT College of Arts and Technology

• Bachelor of Science in Entertainment and Multimedia Computing

KEY PROJECTS

- "Sudoku Showdown!" (2024)
 - **Independently developed** a 3D couch party game inspired by Sudoku using Unity 3D and C#. Implemented backtracking and local multiplayer functionalities.
- "Interweave" (2023)
 - Modeled and textured all 3D assets utilizing Blender, Photoshop, Substance Painter, and Unity for a collaborative horror VR game project inspired by the CIIT college campus.
- "Mistake" (2023)
 - **Lead developer and programmer** for a collaborative 3D story-based game project. Designed 3D map models and developed event branching mechanics.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Consistent Dean's Lister, CIIT College of Arts and Technology (2021 Present)
 - Holder of 3 Gold weave, 1 silver weave, and 7 dean's lister awards.
- Gawad Inabel CIITzen Trailblazer Award (2024)
 - Developed a web application prototype "CIIT's Sales Handling for Organizations Portal".
- Media Recognition: Featured 3D Artist (2022)
 - Featured as a 3D artist on ABS-CBN's KBYN national TV show and in the Philippine Star publication with artwork titled "Almusal".
- First Place in TechnoOlympics: Code Wars, JSMJC Acadaymia Code Wars (2019)
 - Interschool coding competition.
- "Pansin" Best in Short Film, Cinematography, Visual Effects, Sound, and Editing, ARES THEATRUM of ACADAYMIA YEAR 3 (2019)
 - Responsible for filming, directing, and editing.